alexandalexa.com 2012-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Alexandalexa

ALEXANDALEXA.COM ("AA", "we", "our", "us") and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ("you", "your", "yours") and recognise the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We have adopted a Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with.

If you are under 18, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about AA's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering with AA or placing and order with AA.

The following information is provided by AA to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting ALEXANDALEXA.COM, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

  * Exactly what personal information may be collected and by what means 
  * Other information we collect through our services 
  * What about Cookies 
  * How this information may be used, including anyone it might be shared with 
  * Opt-in and opt-out provisions 
  * How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information AA maintains 
  * Safeguarding your personally identifiable data 
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints 
  * Your consent

Please note that this policy applies to AA and/or its subsidiaries, but not to websites maintained by other companies or organisations to which we link. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organisations before submitting any personal information. Furthermore, from time to time AA may employ third party business partners to collect personal information on AA's behalf. In such cases, these third parties will be subject to confidentiality agreements and instructed by AA to fully comply with the AA Privacy Policy as set forth herein.

### Exactly what personal information may be collected about you and by what means?

AA collects personal information in several ways directly from its online visitors when they order for themselves, or when they register for a service offered by AA. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping address(es), credit card billing address(es) and birth date so that we can process and fulfil your orders. Credit card details are entered directly into our Protx Payment Partner's systems and are neither transmitted nor held on AA systems. In certain instances we may be required to collect and store additional data including credit card details. This will only be done with your explicit consent. Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

### Other information we collect through our services

As a user of our services, we may collect non-personal data about use of the website, such as pages visited, times and volume of use of the services as well as Traffic Data. Traffic data includes logs, details of networks, time of log-on or access, length of sessions and similar systems data.

### What about cookies?

Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. (A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser which tracks your movements within websites.) Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items.

### How this information may be used, including anyone it might be shared with

AA may use your personal information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalised shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfil and deliver your orders and manage your account. Your personal information may also be checked with credit agencies to prevent fraud. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body.

When you register with AA, you will be asked if you want to subscribe to our update service. If you choose to opt-in for this service, the information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; contests and events of interest. Similarly, if you choose to opt-in for this service, from time-to-time we will use the information you provide to promote the products and services of our business partners. We do collate statistical information about site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we may pass on to trusted third parties but these statistics do not include any information which can identify you personally. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of your information to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs. If we change our policy on disclosure to others, we will inform you and give you the choice of opting out.

We do occasionally make names and addresses available to companies whose products we think may interest you, unless you have told us not to. If you do not wish to receive such offers please email us at [customerservice@alexandalexa.com](mailto:customerservice@alexandalexa.com)

### Opt-In and Opt-Out Provision

When you register, we will provide a link to the Privacy Policy and consent button for the collection of your personal data. You must register before you can place an order.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of any service to which you have subscribed. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated opt-out link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. In particular, you can opt-out from having your personally identifiable information shared with our business partners or AA's subsidiaries (except as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority or as may be required to deliver your purchases). It is not the Company's current policy to share its customers' personal details with third parties other than as stated herein.

Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database all together, you can do so by sending an e-mail to [customerservice@alexandalexa.com](mailto:customerservice@alexandalexa.com) or by writing to us at: ALEXANDALEXA.COM, Unit L01 (Lincoln Building), The Biscuit Factory, Tower Bridge Business Complex, 100 Clements Road, Bermondsey,London SE16 4DG UK

### How you can access and, if necessary, change your personal information maintained by AA

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by AA is not correct, please visit the web site and, after logging into the site using the "Sign In" menu on the home page; your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you, and/or upon request from you, the Customer Care department can access your personal data from the website using your password and User ID. Information may be changed online within My Details, & Shipping Details, If you prefer to contact us by e-mail at [customerservice@alexandalexa.com](mailto:customerservice@alexandalexa.com), we will amend your personal details.

### Safeguarding your personally identifiable information

We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve you in view of our legitimate business purposes as set out above, and we will use our best endeavours to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. When you place an order or access your account information, we use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption which encrypts your information before it is sent to us to protect it from unauthorised use. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

### Where and how to ask questions or file complaints

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered, if you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and send us an email If you wish to talk to a ALEXANDALEXA.COM customer care representative please call UK 0845 838 1331, US Toll Free on 1855 321 2222 or International +44 (0) 207 232 4200.

### Your consent

By visiting ALEXANDALEXA.COM, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.
